LUKAS GLODEK

07946 780649

lukas.glodek.dev@gmail.com

Profile

Hardworking and enthusiastic Web Developer from Birmingham, currently living in London. Spent last year retraining by completing various projects and online courses using HTML, CSS and Java Script. Holds a degree in Nutrition and Dietetics from Birmingham University and is an experienced English Teacher.

Experience

Web Developer, 2022

- Completed a range of projects using HTML, CSS, Word Press and Java Script.
- Work can be viewed at https://lukas-design.netlify.app

English teacher at "English Connection" in Seville, 2019-2022

- Business English classes in a professional office type environment. Groups consisted of 5-10 students. Classes were focused on improving students ability to use English related to renewable energy and general comprehension.
- Football orientated classes at Real Betis Football club. Due to a big number of students (groups and individuals) classes ranged from professional football vernacular to more general approach. During my time at Real Betis I also participated in an English football camp as a football coach to kids age 7-12.
- Teacher at an academy. Preparing kids and teenagers for a Cambridge exam. Most experience with B1 and B2, but I also worked with A2.

Personal trainer and football coach, B-active gym, Birmingham, 2017-2019

- one to one personal training sessions with clients from various age groups and backgrounds.
- delivered professional workout and nutrition programmes.
- have build an excellent relationship with all clients and children.

English teacher at "speak up", Gdansk, Poland, 2016-2017

- experience in teaching children, teenagers and adults.
- used to working full-time schedule and preparing and delivering classes to a variety of levels and needs.
- successfully prepared students for the exams.

Personal trainer, Cuesta Sport, Seville, June/July 2016

- one to one personal training sessions with clients from all over Europe.
- developed the ability to communicate with clients with limited Spanish.
- gave English lessons through personal training.

Supervisor at Quest Healthcare Limited, 2013-2016

- managed a small team.
- developed ability to present and to give speeches.
- showed great responsibility and organisation by meeting deadlines.

Education

- Birmingham Metropolitan College, Fitness and Personal Training, (2014-2016)
- Birmingham City University, Human Nutrition and Dietetics, (2010-2013)
- Sutton Coldfield College, Birmingham, IT software development, (2006-2008)

Skills

Languages - Native level of both English and Polish. Basic Spanish.

References

Available on request